The city lights are cold tonight
I'm walking under the pale moonlight
I see two people passing by
Reflected in a stranger's eye We're just shadow
dancing A pantomime, a game of chance Trying to
make it look like romance We're just shadow
dancing
Afraid to stop, afraid to fall Just shadows on
the wall
You say the words I want to hear
You whisper love to hide the fear
We're both performing in this play
Hoping the night will turn to day We're just
shadow dancing A pantomime, a game of chance
Trying to make it look like romance We're just
shadow dancing
Afraid to stop, afraid to fall Just shadows on
the wall
Is this real?
I'll never know Just follow where the music goes
Just keep on dancin' We're just shadow dancin' A
pantomime, a game of chess Tryna make it look
like romance We're just shadow dancin'
Afraid to stop, afraid to fall Just shadows on
the wall Shadows
on the wall Shadows dancing